The kettle and the idol
The second one is a one-woman show.
Do you talk to yourself?
I often talk to my make-up artist, my manager, my teacher, etc. I talk to them all the time, not only at work but also at home.
It's not only at work, but also at home.
Sometimes I talk to my mother, and sometimes I talk to myself when she is not around.
When my mother is not around, I talk to her by myself. I'm not talking to myself, I'm talking to the other person.
I'm not talking to myself, I'm talking to the person I'm talking to.
You mean you're basically chatting?
It's all by myself.
It doesn't matter if I don't get any conversation back.
It's a problem.
I'm happy if I can speak up.
I see.
When I don't listen, and I can't hear much because my mom is washing the dishes or something.
I feel satisfied when I can talk and finish.
I guess it's just one step at a time then, right?
I think there might be a lot of conversation.
I think that talking to myself is a good idea when I'm not feeling well, and I feel like I have to work hard.
But I don't think it's good to push myself too hard.
Too much?
Too much.
Pushing too hard.
I think it's not good to push myself too hard. Are you okay? I recently realized that I often say to myself in the mirror, "Are you okay?
To myself in the mirror?
Yes, to myself in the mirror.
To the mirror.
Can you have a conversation? Even in the mirror.
I think I can do it within myself.
It's not easy.
I don't get an answer.
I see.
Is it like that at Sky Tree? As a group.
Yes, it is.
About the setlist, the connection, and so on.
I've noticed recently that I often memorize things by saying them out loud, like the setlist, the connections, etc.
I recently realized that I have to memorize a lot of things by saying them out loud.
I see.
I see. I've been trying to remember what song is next, how to move, how to spend my time, and so on.
I talk by myself all the time about how I'm going to spend my time after that.
It's important, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I think it's pretty important.
I didn't realize I was saying that until then.
I see.
I thought it was a matter of course.
But recently, I've been doing it all the time, even when the dance teacher is around.
Recently, I've had a lot of opportunities for my dance teacher to tell me that Mya talks all the time.
Recently, I've been told that I'm funny.
Is that the case with siblings?
It's a one-way conversation.
I have a habit of talking too long and repeating what I like.
I have a habit of repeating my favorite things.
Favorite phrase? That's right.
When I think I liked it, it's a long conversation.
I repeat it one more time. That scene.
I tell my mom and sister about it, and they say they heard it.
They say, "Hmmm," while watching TV.
I want to tell them.
I want to tell them, but they don't get it.
I want to tell them, but I can't reach them.
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
I think about how I can make my fans happy.
If I were a fan, what would make me happy?
This program was made possible by the participation of Odeko Miya's favorite artists, Ryo-kun, Toshi-san, and
Toshio, Yurigorou, and
Yurigorou, Kei
Kei, Yurigorou, and
Nanana-san, who are all Odeko Miya fans.
We hope you will fall in love with Miya even more!
Thank you very much for your contribution!